Febri Wisnu Fitriandana

Software Developer | IT Support Specialist







Godean, Kab. Sleman, DI Yogyakarta newfebriwisnu@gmail.com

in/newfebriwisnu/

Summary



I am a professional with intermediate-level skills as both a software developer and an IT support specialist. I bring a problem-solving mindset to all my work and have a track record of creating software solutions in a test-driven environment. Additionally, my experience in IT support has equipped me with a deep understanding of technology systems and user support. I am dedicated to keeping abreast of the latest technological developments in both fields.

Work Experiences

Information Technology Developer at RS Mata "Dr. YAP"

February 2022 - Now

- Build and develop software based on company requirements
- Performing tests on software
- Software and hardware maintenance

Digital Marketing Specialist at PropertyToday

September 2020 - December 2021

- Content and Social Media Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Affiliate Marketing

Software Developer at PropertyTodays

September 2020 - December 2021

- Analyzing and designing software
- Build and develop software based on company requirements
- Performing tests on software

Administrator at CV. Dokter Internet Management

July 2015 - December 2016

- Software and hardware maintenance
- Manage daily transactions and reports

Projects

Company Profile and Marketplace Koperasi PropertyToday Indonesia (KPTI)

August 2020 - December 2020

- Create Company Profile
- Marketplace

- UI & UX
- Maintenance
- Stack: PHP Codeigniter, JavaScript, RESTFul API, MySQL

Ads Automation Tools

PropertyToday

February 2021 - March 2021

- Ads Automation Tools
- Development Research
- Report System
- Stack: Python, Selenium, Pandas and RESTful API

Staffing Management Information System (SIMPEG)

RS Queen Latifa

March 2020 - June 2020

- Staffing Management Information System
- Manage Master, Staff Data
- Day Off Leave Management
- Report System
- Stack: PHP Codeigniter, JavaScript, MySQL

RESTful API

December 2020 - December 2020

- Development Research
- Build and Develop
- Documentation
- Stack: PHP, MySQL

Company Profile

Alaric Photography

October 2018 - November 2018

- WordPress Custom
- UI & UX
- Maintenance

Educations

Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta

Informatic Engineering/Bachelor of Informatics Engineering 2020 - GPA: 3.51

SMK Muhammadiyah Seyegan

Software Engineering

2015 - Grade: -

Certifications

Data Engineer

DQLab, March 2022 - April 2022

Python

Cisco Networking Academy, February 2021 - March 2021

Courses

Data Engineer

Pro Academy - Digital Talent Scholarship, March 2022 - April 2022

- Python for Data Professional Beginner
- Data Quality with Python for Beginner
- Data Manipulation with Pandas
- Data Engineer Challenge with SQL

Python

Pro Academy - Digital Talent Scholarship, February 2021 - March 2021

- Data Types, Variables, Basic Input-Output Operations, Basic Operators
- Boolean Values, Conditional Execution, Loops, Lists and List Processing, Logical and Bitwise Operations
- Functions, Tuples, Dictionaries, and Data Processing
- Modules, Packages, PIP
- The Object-Oriented Programming

Skills

IT Support Specialist

Technical Support, IT Hardware Support

Automation

Python (Programming Language), Selenium, Pandas (Python Package), RESTful API

Web Development

PHP, JavaScript, ¡Query, Bootstrap, CodeIgniter, Web SQL Databases, RESTful API